Finding Aid for Post Family Papers 1882-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Marjorie M. Post
  - Alphabetical file
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
      [14-1, etc. to 14-4]
    - Altgelt, Mrs. Woodward Wilson (Box 14)
      [14-5]
    - American Association of University Women (Box 14)
      [14-6]
    - American Committee to Preserve Abu Simbel (Box 14)
      [14-7]
    - American Field Service (Box 14)
      [14-8; 14-9]
    - American Historical Society, re publication of Encyclopedia of American Biography (Box 14)
      [14-10]
    - American Red Cross (Box 14)
      [14-11]
    - American Symphony Orchestra League (Box 14)
      [14-12]
    - American University (Box 14)
      [14-13]
    - Army-Navy Club (Box 14)
      [14-14]
    - Aubusson Rug (Box 14)
      [14-15]
    - Ault, Clyde (property manager) (Box 14)
      [14-16]
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
      [14-17, etc. to 14-20]
    - Barkley, Alben (Box 14)
      [14-21]
    - Barwig, Franz (sculptor) (Box 14)
      [14-22, etc. to 14-26]
    - Battle Creek Enquirer re article about MMP (Box 14)
      [14-27]
    - Battle Creek High School visit to Washington, 1963 (Box 14)
      [14-28; 14-29]
    - Battle Creek (letters from) (Box 14)
      [14-30]
    - Battle Creek (National Symphony visit, 1965) (Box 14)
      [14-31]
    - Battle Creek (dedication of C.W. Post Field, 1961) (Box 14)
      [14-32; 14-33]
    - Battle Creek (Post Tavern art works) (Box 14)
      [14-34]
    - Bavaria, Duke and Duchess of (Box 14)
      [14-35]
    - Belgium (Box 14)
      [14-36]
    - Benefits held at Hillwood (Box 14)
      [14-37]
    - Birley, Sir Oswald and Lady (Box 14)
      [14-38, etc. to 14-41]
    - Bitetto, Princess Cito di (Box 15)
      [15-1]
    - Blair-Lee House (Box 15)
      [15-2]
    - Blake, Theodore (architect) (Box 15)
      [15-3]
    - Blind (associations for the) (Box 15)
      [15-4]
    - "Boulders" (Greenwich, Conn. home) (Box 15)
      [15-5]
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 15)
      [15-6, etc. to 5-9]
    - Brabourne, Lady Doreen (Box 15)
      [15-10, etc. to 15-12]
    - Broun, Rahel (Box 15)
      [15-13]
    - Buchanan, Hon. Wiley (Box 15)
      [15-14]
    - Bucknell University (Box 15)
      [15-15]
    - Bulman, Orville (Box 15)
      [15-16]
    - Burke, Billie (Box 15)
      [15-17, etc. to 15-21]
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
      [15-22, etc. to 15-25]
    - Cangero family (Box 15)
      [15-26]
    - Cantacuzene, Princess Julia (Box 15)
      [15-27]
    - Carmichael, Leonard (Box 15)
      [15-28]
    - Cemeteries (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
      [15-29]
    - Cemetery (Springfield, Illinois) (Box 15)
      [15-30]
    - Cemetery (Cornwall, Vermont) (Box 15)
      [15-31]
    - Chandor, Mrs. Douglas (Box 15)
      [15-32]
    - Chester, Colby, Jr. (Box 15)
      [15-33]
    - Chile, Embassy of (Box 15)
      [15-34]
    - Christian Science (Box 15)
      [15-35]
    - Clifford, Sir Bede and Lady (Box 15)
      [15-36, etc. to 15-38]
    - Close, Adelaide (Box 16)
      [16-1]
    - Close, Eleanore (Box 16)
      [16-2]
    - Close, Marjorie (Box 16)
      [16-3]
    - Coat of Arms (Merriweather Post) (Box 16)
      [16-4]
    - Coles, Mrs. Marvin (Box 16)
      [16-5]
    - Columbia, Maryland (Merriweather Post Pavilion of Music) (Box 16)
      [16-6]
    - Columbia University (Box 16)
      [16-7]
    - Columbia University tape recording data (Box 16)
      [no folder number]
    - Congressional Record (Box 16)
      [16-8]
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
      [16-9]
    - Davies, Joseph (appointment to Russia) (Box 16)
      [16-10]
    - Davies, Joseph (General) (Box 16)
      [16-11, etc. to 16-13]
    - DeFels, Countess Andre (Box 16)
      [16-14]
    - DeMammos, Mrs. Ronald (Box 16)
      [16-15]
    - Depression (Feeding stations) (Box 16)
      [16-16]
    - Dignitaries (Box 16)
      [16-17, etc. to 16-19]
    - Diplomatic Assistance Committee (Box 16)
      [16-20]
    - Distinguished Women of Washington (Box 16)
      [16-21]
    - Ditzen, Dr. Lowell R. (Box 16)
      [16-22]
    - Dover Publications (C.W. Post portrait) (Box 16)
      [16-23]
    - Dudley, Henry A. (Box 16)
      [16-24]
    - Dunlop Photographers (Box 16)
      [16-25, etc. to 16-27]
    - Durant, Tim (Box 16)
      [16-28]
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
      [16-29]
    - Eisenhower, President and Mrs. (Box 16)
      [16-30]
    - Elliott, Maxine (Box 16)
      [16-31]
    - Encyclopedia of American Biography (Box 16)
      [16-32]
    - English-speaking Union (Box 16)
      [16-33]
    - Eriksson, Capt. Evert (Box 16)
      [16-34]
    - Evans, R.B. Wilson (British American Society) (Box 16)
      [16-35]
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
      [16-36; 16-37]
    - Face Creams (Box 16)
      [16-38]
    - Family (financial) (Box 16)
      [16-39]
    - Fan letters (Box 16)
      [16-40, etc. to 16-42]
    - Fish protein cookies (Box 16)
      [16-43]
    - Florida Board of Control (Mar-A-Lago) (Box 17)
      [17-1]
    - Florida (Honorary citizenship) (Box 17)
      [17-2]
    - Folsom, Merrill (Box 17)
      [17-3]
    - Fox, Virgil (Box 17)
      [17-4]
    - France, Embassy of (Box 17)
      [17-5]
    - France (Salute to) (Box 17)
      [17-6]
    - Friendship House benefit, 1964 (Box 17)
      [17-7]
    - Fry, Marshall (Box 17)
      [17-8]
    - Fulton, James (Box 17)
      [17-9]
    - Furniture (Box 17)
      [17-10]
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
      [17-11]
    - Gardner, Mrs. John J. (Box 17)
      [17-12]
    - Girl Scouts (Box 17)
      [17-13]
    - General Foods Corporation (Box 17)
      [17-14, etc. to 17-22]
    - Greece, Embassy of (Box 17)
      [17-23]
    - Greek Relief Fund (Box 17)
      [17-24]
    - Griffin, James B. (Box 17)
      [17-25]
    - Gruver (Edward F.) Co. (Box 17)
      [17-26]
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
      [17-27; 17-28]
    - Harper Method (hair treatment) (Box 17)
      [17-29]
    - Hereditary Societies (Box 17)
      [17-30, etc. to 17-32]
    - Hillwood (Flagstaff dedication) (Box 17)
      [17-33; 17-34]
    - Hillwood (Friendship Walk) (Box 17)
      [17-35]
    - Hillwood (Gardens booklet) (Box 17)
      [17-36]
    - Hillwood (Food costs) (Box 17)
      [17-37]
    - Hillwood (Tea lists) (Box 18)
      [18-1]
    - Hillwood (origin) (Box 18)
      [18-2]
    - Hillwood (adjoining lands) (Box 18)
      [18-3]
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges (Box 18)
      [18-4]
    - Hoxie, R. Gordon (Box 18)
      [18-5]
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 18)
      [18-6]
    - Hutton
      - Barbara Hutton (Box 18)
        [18-7; 18-8]
      - Nedenia Hutton (Box 18)
        [18-9]
      - E.F. and Marjorie Post Hutton 1920s; 1930s (Box 18)
        [18-10, etc. to 18-22]
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
      [18-23]
    - India, Embassy of (Box 18)
      [18-24]
    - International Club of Washington, D.C. (Box 18)
      [18-25]
    - Italy, Embassy of (Box 18)
      [18-26]
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
      [18-27]
    - James, Charles (Box 18)
      [18-28]
    - Japan, Embassy of (Box 18)
      [18-29]
    - Jewels (Box 18)
      [18-30]
    - Johanson, Carlton A. and Jane (Box 18)
      [18-31; 18-32]
    - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon (Box 18)
      [18-33]
    - Jonsson, Ambassador Ake (Box 18)
      [18-34]
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
      [18-35]
    - Kawananakoa, Princess (Box 19)
      [19-1]
    - Keenan, Thomas S. and James G. Keenan (Box 19)
      [19-2]
    - Kennedy family (Box 19)
      [19-3]
    - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (Box 19)
      [19-4, etc. to 19-8]
    - Knights of the Garter (Box 19)
      [19-9]
    - Knights of Malta (Box 19)
      [19-10]
    - Knotts, Judge James (Box 19)
      [19-11; 19-12]
    - Korth, Fred (Box 19)
      [19-13, etc. to 19-15]
    - Kuruso, Madame and family (Box 19)
      [19-16]
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
      [19-17]
    - Lane, Miss Marguerite (Box 19)
      [19-18]
    - LaPierre, Mrs. Guy (Box 19)
      [19-19]
    - Legion of Honor Presentation (Box 19)
      [19-20]
    - Life Magazine (proposed story) (Box 19)
      [19-21]
    - Lincoln Memorial (Box 19)
      [19-22]
    - Logan, John A. and Polly (Box 19)
      [19-23]
    - Loy, Earl (Box 19)
      [19-24]
    - Luxembourg (Box 19)
      [19-25]
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
      [19-26]
    - McAuliffe, General A.C. (Box 19)
      [19-27]
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
      [19-28, etc. to 19-30]
    - Major, Nettie (Box 19)
      [19-31, etc. to 19-38]
    - Marine Corps League (Box 20)
      [20-1]
    - Marshall, Mrs. George C. (Box 20)
      [20-2]
    - Marston, Hunter (Box 20)
      [20-3]
    - Matsas, Helene (Box 20)
      [20-4]
    - May, Herbert (wedding) (Box 20)
      [20-5]
    - May, Herbert (Box 20)
      [20-6, etc. to 20-10]
    - Merriweather family (genealogical) (Box 20)
      [20-11]
    - Modig, Gus (Box 20)
      [20-12]
    - Montgomery, Kenneth F. (Box 20)
      [20-13]
    - Morrow, William L. (Box 20)
      [20-14]
    - Moffat, Margaret (Box 20)
      [20-15]
    - Mount Vernon Guard (Box 20)
      [20-16]
    - Mount Vernon Seminary, Washington, D.C. (Box 20)
      [20-17, etc. to 20-21]
    - Mount Vernon Seminary, Pittsburgh (Box 20)
      [20-22]
    - Murray, Arthur (dance studios) (Box 20)
      [20-23]
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
      [20-24]
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 20)
      [20-25]
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography (Box 20)
      [20-26]
    - National Federation of Music Clubs (Box 20)
      [20-27]
    - National Gallery of Art (Box 20)
      [20-28]
    - National Geographic Society (Box 20)
      [20-29]
    - National Institute of Social Sciences (Box 20)
      [20-30]
    - National Savings and Trust Company (Box 20)
      [20-31]
    - National Society of Arts and Letters (Box 20)
      [20-32]
    - National Society of Interior Designers (Box 20)
      [20-33]
    - National Symphony Orchestra (Box 20)
      [20-34, etc. to 20-39]
    - National Symphony Orchestra (Box 21)
      [21-1, etc. to 21-4]
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 21)
      [21-5]
    - Needle and Bobbin Club (Box 21)
      [21-6]
    - Nerinex, Ida (Box 21)
      [21-7]
    - Netherlands, Embassy of (Box 21)
      [21-8]
    - Newbern, Dr. Walter (Box 21)
      [21-9]
    - Niculescu, Katherine Ross (Box 21)
      [21-10]
    - Nine O'clocks of New York (Box 21)
      [21-11]
    - Nixon, President and Mrs. Richard M. (Box 21)
      [21-12]
    - Norton, Myra (Box 21)
      [21-13]
    - Norway, Crown Prince of (Box 21)
      [21-14]
    - Norway, King of (Haakan) (Box 21)
      [21-15]
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
      [21-16]
    - Obolensky, Serge (Box 21)
      [21-17]
    - Oliver, John (Box 21)
      [21-18]
    - Opera Society of Washington (Box 21)
      [21-19]
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
      [21-20; 21-21]
    - Perkins, Daniels and McCormack (law firm) (Box 21)
      [21-22]
    - Philanthropies (Box 21)
      [21-23; etc. to 21-37]
    - Hotel Pierre Apartment (Box 21)
      [21-38, etc. to 21-41]
    - Pittsburgh "Rosewall" (Box 21)
      [21-42]
    - Portugal, Embassy of (Box 21)
      [21-43]
    - Post book plate (Box 21)
      [21-44]
    - Post (Carrie Post King's Daughters' Home for Women) (Box 21)
      [21-45]
    - Post, Carroll L. (Box 21)
      [21-46]
    - Post, Carroll L. (monument) (Box 21)
      [21-47]
    - Post, C.W. (Box 22)
      [22-1]
    - Post (C.W.) Collection, Battle Creek (Box 22)
      [22-2]
    - Post, Charles W. (son of John H. Post) (Box 22)
      [22-3; 22-4]
    - Post, Fammie (Box 22)
      [22-5]
    - Post Foundation (Box 22)
      [22-6]
    - Post, Marjorie Merriweather
      - Biographical (Box 22)
        [22-7]
      - Biographical (requests) (Box 22)
        [22-8]
      - Birthdays (Box 22)
        [22-9, etc. to 22-17]
      - Citations and awards (Box 22)
        [22-18, etc. to 22-24]
      - Correspondence (Box 22)
        [22-25; 22-26]
      - Confidential (Box 22)
        [22-27]
      - Court presentation (Box 22)
        [22-28]
      - Death preparations (Box 22)
        [22-29, etc. to 22-31]
      - Debut party for Diane Hull (Box 22)
        [22-32]
      - Donations of furnishings (Box 22)
        [22-33, etc. to 22-38]
      - Membership cards (Box 22)
        [22-39]
      - Music (Box 22)
        [22-40]
      - Oral history re her father C.W. Post (Box 22)
        [22-41]
      - Portraits (Box 22)
        [22-42]
      - Publications (Box 22)
        [22-43]
      - Speeches (Box 22)
        [22-44]
      - Wedding June 18, 1958, to Herbert May (Box 23)
        [23-1]
    - Post City, Texas (Box 23)
      [23-2, etc. to 23-11]
    - C.W. Post College (Box 23)
      [23-12, etc. to 23-26]
    - Post-Montgomery, Texas (Box 23)
      [23-27]
    - Post, Russell B. (Box 23)
      [23-28]
    - "Prophecies of the Pyramids" (Box 23)
      [23-29]
    - Q (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
      [23-30]
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
      [24-1]
    - Raymond, Mr. and Mrs. Gene (Box 24)
      [24-2]
    - Reid, Whitelaw and Ogden Reid (Box 24)
      [24-3]
    - Reynick, Mrs. Henry F. (Box 24)
      [24-4]
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor and Franklin Roosevelt (Box 24)
      [24-5]
    - Ross, Marvin C. (Box 24)
      [24-6]
    - Rosso, Frances (Box 24)
      [24-7]
    - Rumbough, David (Box 24)
      [24-8]
    - Rumbough, Nina (Box 24)
      [24-9]
    - Russell, Edward H. (Box 24)
      [24-10]
    - Russia, Embassy of (Box 24)
      [24-11]
    - Russian War Relief (World War II) (Box 24)
      [24-12]
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
      [24-13; 24-14]
    - Salisbury, Frank O. (Box 24)
      [24-15; 24-16]
    - Salvation Army (Box 24)
      [24-17]
    - Saud, King of Arabia (Box 24)
      [24-18]
    - Scampi (pet dog) (Box 24)
      [24-19]
    - Schwartz, Bernard (Box 24)
      [24-20]
    - Shakespeare Summer Festival (Box 24)
      [24-21]
    - Sibley family (Box 24)
      [24-22, etc. to 24-29]
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity, C.W. Post College (Box 24)
      [24-30, etc. to 24-32]
    - Sigma Alpha Theta sorority, C.W. Post College (Box 24)
      [24-33; 24-34]
    - Sloanaker, Hiram L. (Box 25)
      [25-1]
    - Smith, Douglas (Box 25)
      [25-2]
    - Smithsonian (Box 25)
      [25-3; 25-4]
    - Society of Cincinnati (Box 25)
      [25-5]
    - South Plains College, Levelland, Texas (Box 25)
      [25-6]
    - Spain, Embassy of (Box 25)
      [25-7]
    - State Department (Fine Arts Committee) (Box 25)
      [25-8]
    - Stoney, Mrs. Theodore (Box 25)
      [25-9]
    - Stotesbury (Box 25)
      [25-10]
    - Sulgrave Club (Box 25)
      [25-11]
    - Sutton Place, Surrey, England (Box 25)
      [25-12]
    - Sweden (Box 25)
      [25-13]
    - Sylvia, Marguerita (Box 25)
      [25-14]
    - Syme, Jane (Box 25)
      [25-15]
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
      [25-16]
    - Texas (Box 25)
      [25-17]
    - Thayer, Mollie (Box 25)
      [25-18]
    - Thode, Mrs. John F. (Box 25)
      [25-19]
    - Time Magazine, February 1967 (Box 25)
      [25-20]
    - Town and Country Magazine (Box 25)
      [25-21; 25-22]
    - Traveler's Aid Benefit 1965 (Box 25)
      [25-23]
    - Travels
      - South American Cruise 1948, 1950 (Box 25)
        [25-24]
      - European trip 1950 (Box 25)
        [25-25]
      - Coronation trip to England 1953 (Box 25)
        [25-26]
      - European trip 1954 (Box 25)
        [25-27]
      - North Cape cruise 1958 (Box 25)
        [25-28]
      - Miscellaneous 1958 (Box 25)
        [25-29]
      - European trip 1960-1961 (Box 25)
        [25-30]
      - Mediterranean cruise 1964 (Box 25)
        [25-31]
      - Spain and Portugal, 1966-1967 (Box 25)
        [25-32]
      - Italy (Ischia), (cancelled) 1970 (Box 25)
        [25-33]
      - Gripsholm (Christmas cruise), 1970 (Box 25)
        [25-34]
      - Homestead, Hot Springs, Va., 1972 (Box 25)
        [25-35]
    - Trudeau family (Box 25)
      [25-36]
    - Truman, Harry S and Bess Truman (Box 25)
      [25-37]
    - Turkey, Embassy of (Box 25)
      [25-38]
    - Tydings, Eleanor (Box 25)
      [25-39, etc. to 25-43]
    - Tydings family (Box 25)
      [25-44]
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
      [26-1]
    - United States Committee for the United Nations (Box 26)
      [26-2]
    - United States Naval Academy (Box 26)
      [26-3]
    - Urbar, Mary (Box 26)
      [26-4]
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
      [26-5]
    - VanZandt family (Box 26)
      [26-6]
    - Variety Club, Pittsburgh (Box 26)
      [26-7]
    - Vietnam Veterans Partys (Box 26)
      [26-8, etc. to 26-14]
    - Vogel, Frances (Box 26)
      [26-15]
    - Voight, Margaret (Box 26)
      [26-16]
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
      [26-17; 26-18]
    - Walker, Una (Box 26)
      [26-19]
    - Watson, Roy and Katherine Watson (Box 26)
      [26-20]
    - Wennergren Axel, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 26)
      [26-21]
    - Whalen, Grover (Box 26)
      [26-22]
    - Whilar, Milton J. (Box 26)
      [26-23]
    - White, Anne (Box 26)
      [26-24]
    - Whitney, Eleanor (Box 26)
      [26-25]
    - Who's Who (Box 26)
      [26-26]
    - Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 26)
      [26-27]
    - Windsor, Duke and Duchess (Box 26)
      [26-28]
    - Winston, Harry Inc. (Box 26)
      [26-29]
    - Woman's National Democratic Club (Box 26)
      [26-30]
    - Wood, William R. (Box 26)
      [26-31]
    - Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation, Inc. (Box 26)
      [26-32]
    - World Nobility and Peerage (Box 26)
      [26-33]
    - Wright, Suzanne (Box 26)
      [26-34]
    - X,Y, Z (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
      [26-35]
    - Yacht charter, proposed (Box 26)
      [26-36]
  - Residences
    The Residences series includes information on the acquisition, construction and remodeling, maintenance and use of Marjorie Post's estates and apartments.
    - Sheraton East (New York apartment) (Box 26)
    - 2 East 92nd Street, New York (Box 26)
    - Rosalyn, Long Island, New York (including material on its sale to Long Island University) (Box 26)
    - Tregaron, Washington, D.C. (Box 27)
    - Camp Topridge (in the Adirondacks, New York state) (Box 27)
    - Mar-A-Lago (Palm Beach, Florida) (Box 28)
    - Mar-A-Lago (Palm Beach, Florida) (Box 29)
      (continued)
    - Mar-A-Lago (Palm Beach, Florida) (Box 30)
  - Means of transport
    The Means of Transport series includes information on the various airplanes, yachts and luxury automobiles owned by Post and her husbands.
    - Automobiles and baggage car (Box 30)
    - Airplanes (largely concerning the Merriweather) (Box 30)
    - Yacht (concerning the Sea Cloud) (Box 31)
  - Clippings and Miscellaneous
    The Clippings and Miscellaneous subseries includes copies of a LIFE magazine profile of Marjorie Post and the extensive correspondence it generated, along with numerous other newspaper and magazine clippings in which Post is mentioned. Also included are various citations and awards presented to Post, obituaries, and several scrapbooks relating to John Davies diplomatic career and Post involvement with the Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee Campaign of 1932.
    - Life Magazine article on Marjorie M. Post, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Letters received in response to Life Magazine article
      [arranged alphabetically by state]
      - Alabama-Pennsylvania (Box 32)
      - Rhode Island-Wyoming (Box 33)
      - Foreign letters (Box 33)
        [arranged alphabetically by country]
    - Magazine articles containing references to Marjorie M. Post (Box 33)
    - Newspaper clippings re Marjorie M. Post (Box 34)
    - Programs and other published memorabilia (Box 34)
    - Funeral material (Box 35)
    - Obituaries and other articles upon death (Box 35)
    - Citations, honorary degrees, and tributes (Box 36)
    - Examples of dinner guest lists (Box 36)
    - Original proposal for disposition of Mar-A-Lago to the state of Florida (Box 36)
    - Birthday greetings (Box 36)
    - Scrapbooks concerning diplomatic career of Joseph Davies, 2 volumes (Box 37)
    - Scrapbooks concerning diplomatic career of Joseph Davies, 3 volumes (Box 38)
    - C.W. Post College (Box 39)
    - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee Campaign 1932, 3 volumes (Box 39)
    - Post Theatre Opening 1902 (Box 39)
    - Blair House Fine Arts Committee (Box 39)
    - Post Company Band (Box 39)
    - C.W. Post Field, Battle Creek (Box 39)
    - Post Golden Jubilee, Post, Texas (Box 39)
    - Harry R. Davidson's trip to Russia 1964 (Box 39)
    - Music for Young America (Box 40)
    - Lord Duveen's Instruction in Art for Marjorie M. Post (Box 40)
    - Baby and early school books (Box 40)
    - "Boulders" account book 1909 (Box 41)
    - Mission to Moscow (autographed by cast film) (Box 41)
    - C.W. Post; The Hour and the Man (Box 41)
    - Card indexes to C.W. Post and M.M. Post papers (compiled by L. Majors) (Box 41)
  - Post family materials
    The Post family materials includes some correspondence with and biographical and genealogical information about various members of the Post family
    - Truman Post (Box 42)
    - C. Rollin Post (Box 42)
    - Carrie Post (Box 42)
    - Ella Post (Box 43)
    - Carroll Lathrop Post (Box 43)
    - Genealogical and related material (Box 43)
    - Post City, Texas (Box 43)
    - Microfilm copies of selective portions of C.W. Post and Marjorie M. Post (Box 44)
  - Nettie Major-Sayles Accession 1983
    The Nettie Major-Sayles subseries is comprised of material created or collected by Major-Sayles in preparation of a biography of Post.
    - Biographies (Box 47)
      - C.W. Post (Box 47)
      - Marjorie Meriweather Post (Box 47)
      - Others (Box 47)
    - Correspondence
      - General 1961-1975 (Box 47)
      - Bentley Historical Library, 1969-1981 (Box 47)
      - Meyer Handelman, 1965-1971 (Box 47)
    - Family history
      - Family Bibles (Box 47)
      - Genealogical research, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Heraldry (Box 47)
    - Interviews
      - Interviews with Marjorie Meriweather Post, 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Interviews about Marjorie Meriweather Post (Box 47)
    - Newspaper clippings, 5 folders (Box 47)
    - Properties
      - Hillwood (Box 47)
      - Mar-A-Lago (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Audio-recordings (tapes and phonorecords) of interviews with Marjorie M. Post and others
    [STAFF USE ONLY; use cassette copies in box 50]
    The audio recordings consist of interviews with Marjorie Post and others, mostly concerning the design, construction and maintenance of Post's residences and estates.
    [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    - Dedication ceremonies at Post, Texas, 1957 September 17, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (On the subject of "C.W. Post, Man of Vision, Creative Imagination, and Courage." Begins with a speech by a Dr. Wiggins, remainder of the tape is a speech by unnamed female speaker.)
    - Interview of Marjorie Merriweather Post, 1962 February 19, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3.75
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (On the subject of Mar-A-Lago, Boulders, New York apartments, and Camp Topridge.)
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (On the subject of Mar-A-Lago, Boulders, New York apartments, and Camp Topridge.)
    - Interview of Marjorie Merriweather Post, 1962 March 17, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3.75
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-3-1]; mp3 file; (On the subject of New York house and apartments, Russia, etc. to Rosewall.)
    - Interview of Marjorie Merriweather Post, 1965 February, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3.75
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-4-1-1]; mp3 file; (On the subject of Palm Beach, Florida.)
      - [Part 1], [85519-SR-4-1-2]; mp3 file; (On the subject of Palm Beach, Florida.)